20B, FEMITI OLUWA QTRS OKE ODO ALAPATA, OLOSAN, ALAKIA, IBADAN. 07066746133 bharyhour@gmail.com

ABDULWAHAB UTHMAN BAYONLE

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

A young, experienced and dedicated pharmacist with demonstrated success in pharmaceutical services. Bringing forth a strong background in clinical pharmacy and medication management. Extensive knowledge of pharmacy operations, pharmacy management and medications. Strong communication skills, well-developed time management skill and significant ability to work under pressure.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- Pharmaceutical operations.
- Patient counselling.
- Comprehensive clinical awareness.
- Excellent interpersonal and Team management skills.
- Proficient user of IT.

EXPERIENCE

ALPHA PHARMACY AND STORES LIMITED, IKEJA, LAGOS STATE

September 2017- February 2018

- Stock taking and dispensing of medications.
- Filled and verified prescriptions under the supervision of a superintendent pharmacy.
- Treated patients with sensitivity and respect for their privacy.
- Counselled patients on product safety and administration.

INDUSTRIAL TRAINEE - UNIVERSITY COLLEGE HOSPITAL (UCH) IBADAN,

October 2018- January 2019

- Collaborated with the hospital Accident and Emergency, Spill-over wards, APIN Clinic etc.
- Interpreted, validated and dispensed medications according to the treatment sheet medication order to each ward.
- Engaged in proper documentation where necessary.

PHARMACIST - HEALTHSPRINGS PHARMACY, 11 OWEH STREET, FADEYI, LAGOS STATE

January 2020- February 2020

- Reviewed physician prescriptions to assess accuracy and safety.
- Filled and verified prescriptions.
- Treated patients with sensitivity and respect for their privacy.
- Counselled patients on product safety and administration.

PHARMACIST – HERMON PHARMCARE, NO 1 OSOSAMI STREET, ADEOYO ROUNDABOUT, RING ROAD IBADAN.

June 2020 - Present

- Reviewed physician prescriptions to assess accuracy and safety.
- Filled and verified prescriptions.
- Treated patients with sensitivity and respect for their privacy
- Counselled patients on product safety and administration.

INTERN PHARMACIST - RING ROAD STATE HOSPITAL, ADEOYO ROAD, IBADAN.

September 2020 - Present

- Interpreting, validating and dispensation of medications according to the treatment sheet medication order to each ward and out-patient prescription.
- Engaging in proper documentation where necessary.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF LAGOS (B.PHARM), PHARMACY (2014 – 2019)

FEDERAL GOVERNMENT COLLEGE OGBOMOSHO (S.S.C.E) 2013

AD-DIN INTERNATIONAL COLLEGE (J.S.C.E) 2010

COMMUNICATION

- Good communication skill.
- Fluent in English and Yoruba.

LEADERSHIP

(2012 -2013) Health Prefect

Federal Government College Ogbomosho Oyo State

(2016-2017) Member

Electoral Committee Faculty of Pharmacy UNILAG

(2017-2018) Vice President Pharmaceutical Association of

Nigerian Students (UNILAG CHAPTER).

(2018-2019) Deputy Chairman

Electoral Committee College of Medicine and Pharmaceutical

Sciences Student Association

REFERENCES

DR N. H IGBOKWE

DEPARTMENT OF PHARMACEUTICS AND PHARMACEUTICAL TECHNOLOGY

FACULTY OF PHARMACY, UNILAG

08023328313